Next on the glue console,
scroll down on the left hand side, click on crawlers,
click on create crawler name the crawler S mission
D-E-H-H-O-F-N-Y-C-D-L-C-H-V-F-H-V.
And then scroll down. Click on next.
So now we are creating crawler to crawl the file
to crawl this F-H-V-H-V Trip
data file.
We wanna crawl the file so that the crawler can create
a metadata table, a structure on the the Parquet file.
The file is in the history bucket.
So we're gonna go to glue again.
And here you're gonna scroll down, add the data source.
And right here we're gonna scroll down
and put the S3 path right here.
And to get the full path, we're gonna go to S3 again.
And the file is here in this folder, H-V-F-H-V.
So I'm gonna scroll up and click on the copy. S3 URI button.
Click on that. It's copied. I'm gonna go back to blue.
Paste it right here. It might show you in red here.
Now click on the red itself and then come down.
And then click on add data.
Add an S3 data source,
and you'll see the S3 data source right here.
And then scroll down, click on Next.
You'd already have an IM role called as Mission.
DHH of Glue Service role. Choose that mission. D-H-H-O-F.
Glue Service role. This was created when you ran the script
before in the cloud Shell in the real world.
You would be given to this
by your teammate or your team lead.
And then you scroll down, click on next here.
Choose the database that you created in the previous step,
which was Mission, D-H-H-O-F-N-Y-C-T-L-C.
Write the table name, prefix as H-E-F-H-V.
And then scroll down. Click on next.
On the next page, review and create.
Scroll down, click on Create Crawler.
And then finally, when you see this,
click on the run crawler here.
This will show you it is successfully starting. Starting.
And then scroll down and refresh this here.
You'll see it is already running right here.
In fact, wait for it to finish.
It'll take about a minute or two.